But then a miracle happened.
但是奇迹发生了
I saw a bubble
我看见了一个气泡
rising to the surface,
升到了表面
and I had this powerful urge to follow it up to the light.
这给了我如此强烈的欲望 要追随它去往光明
I was so scared.
我内心充满了恐惧
I didn't know how I could stay still.
我不知道怎样才能静止不动
But then the light became so bright.
但接着那道光变得如此耀眼
I was lost in it,
我迷失在了其中
in the warmth and peace.
迷失在了一片温暖与祥和之中
It was Jesus.
那是耶稣
I had known him my whole life,but I truly met him that day.
我认识他一辈子了 但在那天我才真的见到
I floated out of my body,held aloft by the wings of an angel.
我的意识游离出了身体 被天使的翅膀捧在高处
From above, I saw him cut off my ear, but I gave him nothing.
在高处  我看见他割下我的耳朵  但我什么反应也没有
Not a twitch or a sound.
我纹丝不动  没发出一点声响
And that's how I managed to survive, through the grace of God ,and His mercy.
我就是这样活下来的 多亏了上帝的恩典